cpaoffers.com 2012-10-01

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy sets out how [CPAoffers.com](http://cpaoffers.com/) uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully and in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.

When we ask you to provide information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Our privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically for updates.

## What Information We Collect

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The type of information we may collect about you includes:

  * Your name
  * Your email address

## How We Use This Data

We only send promotional emails if you have explicitly double opted-in. We do not sell, rent or share email addresses etc. We will only share personal information when required by law or when you have explicitly requested that we do so (e.g. made a sales enquiry that would require us to pass your details to a supplier).

We require this information to provide you with a better service. In particular, for the following reasons:

  * To improve our products and services
  * Technical support
  * Service announcements
  * To customise your user experience

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Cookies

We may use your IP address for several reasons: to help diagnose server problems, to administer our website, to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information using webstats packages, like Google Analytics. This uses cookies.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use cookies for various reasons, including software such as:

  * Google Analytics
  * CrazyEgg.com
  * OpenX ad server

Cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## External Links

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Personal Information

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the address listed in CPAoffers.com’s WHOIS record.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us immediately. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Any Questions?

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.cpaoffers.com/contact-us.php).
